noulinx.com 2014-05-23

# NouLinx - Privacy policy

Privacy Policy

This privacy policy regards how we store and deal with your user information.  
As a registered member at NouLinx, you have agreed to have read, understood, and accepted the following terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**What information do we collect?**

We collect the minimum amount of information about you that is commensurate with providing you with a satisfactory service.

We may collect any or all of the information that you give us depending on the type of transaction you enter into, including email address, birth year together with data about your use of the website. Other information that may be needed from time to time to process a request may also be collected as indicated on the website. Your use of this website gives us the right to collect that information. 

**How we use the collect information?**

We use the information collected primarily to process the task for which you visited the website. All reasonable precautions are taken to prevent unauthorised access to this information. This safeguard may require you to provide additional forms of identity should you wish to obtain information about your account. 

**Do we use cookies?**

We use Cookies (small files placed on your hard drive through your web browser that enables us to recognize you, capture and remember certain information). You have the ability to prevent your computer from accepting cookies but, if you do, certain functionality on the website may be impaired. 

**Disclosing Information**

We do not disclose any personal information obtained about you from this website to third parties except when we need to do so in order to complete the transaction. We may also use the information to keep in contact with you. If at any time in the future we should wish to disclose information collected on this website to any third party, it would only be with your knowledge and consent.  
We may provide information of a general nature to third parties, for example, the number of individuals visiting our website or registred users, but we will not use any information that could identify those individuals.
